	questionList = questionList.concat([
	
	//Imperfect  6
	{question:"The boy was eating.", answers:["El niño comía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"The boy used to eat.", answers:["El niño comía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"El niño comía.", answers:["The boy used to eat.", "The child used to eat.", "The boy was eating.","The child was eating."], language:"English"},
	{question:"The man was eating.", answers:["El hombre comía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"The man used to eat.", answers:["El hombre comía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú bebías agua.", answers:["You were drinking water.","You used to drink water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You were drinking water.", answers:["Tú bebías agua.","Bebías agua.","Usted bebía agua.","Ustedes bebían agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"You used to drink water.", answers:["Tú bebías agua.","Bebías agua.","Usted bebía agua.","Ustedes bebían agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo comía.", answers:["I was eating.","I used to eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I was eating.", answers:["Comía.","Yo comía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Un niño bebía.", answers:["A boy was drinking.","A child was drinking.","A boy used to drink.","A child used to drink."], language:"English"},
	{question:"A boy was drinking.", answers:["Un niño bebía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"A boy used to drink.", answers:["Un niño bebía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Yo bebía.", answers:["I was drinking.","I used to drink."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I was drinking.", answers:["Yo bebía.", "Bebía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"I used to drink.", answers:["Yo bebía.", "Bebía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú comías.", answers:["You were eating.","You used to eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You were eating.", answers:["Tú comías.", "Comías.", "Usted comía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"You used to eat.", answers:["Tú comías.", "Comías.", "Usted comía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Nosotras bebíamos leche.", answers:["We were drinking milk.","We used to drink milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros bebíamos leche.", answers:["We were drinking milk.","We used to drink milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We were drinking milk.", answers:["Bebíamos leche.", "Nosotros bebíamos leche.", "Nosotras bebíamos leche."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We used to drink milk.", answers:["Bebíamos leche.", "Nosotros bebíamos leche.", "Nosotras bebíamos leche."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotras bebíamos agua.", answers:["We were drinking water.","We used to drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros bebíamos agua.", answers:["We were drinking water.","We used to drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We were drinking water.", answers:["Bebíamos agua.", "Nosotros bebíamos agua.", "Nosotras bebíamos agua."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We used to drink water.", answers:["Bebíamos agua.", "Nosotros bebíamos agua.", "Nosotras bebíamos agua."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You were drinking water.", answers:["Tú bebías agua.", "Bebías agua.", "Usted bebía agua.", "Ustedes bebían agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"You used to drink water.", answers:["Tú bebías agua.", "Bebías agua.", "Usted bebía agua.", "Ustedes bebían agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ustedes bebían agua.", answers:["You used to drink water.","You were drinking water."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"You were drinking milk.", answers:["Tú bebías leche.","Bebías leche.","Usted bebía leche.","Ustedes bebían leche."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"You used to drink milk.", answers:["Tú bebías leche.","Bebías leche.","Usted bebía leche.","Ustedes bebían leche."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"They used to drink.", answers:["Bebían.","Ellos bebían.","Ellas bebían."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"They were drinking.", answers:["Bebían.","Ellos bebían.","Ellas bebían."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos bebían.", answers:["They were drinking.","They used to drink."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Las niñas bebían agua.", answers:["The girls were drinking water.","The children were drinking water.","The girls used to drink water.","The children used to drink water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls were drinking water.", answers:["Las niñas bebían agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"The girls used to drink water.", answers:["Las niñas bebían agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Los niños bebían agua.", answers:["The boys were drinking water.","The children were drinking water.","The boys used to drink water.","The children used to drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"The boys were drinking water.", answers:["Los niños bebían agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"The boys used to drink water.", answers:["Los niños bebían agua."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Tú escribías un libro.", answers:["You were writing a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You were writing a book.", answers:["Tú escribías un libro.","Escribías un libro.","Usted escribía un libro.","Ustedes escribían un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Usted escribía un libro.", answers:["You were writing a book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Yo escribía una carta.", answers:["I was writing a letter."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"I was writing a letter.", answers:["Yo escribía una carta.","Escribía una carta."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Nosotros escribíamos un libro.", answers:["We were writing a book."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"We were writing a book.", answers:["Nosotros escribíamos un libro.","Nosotras escribíamos un libro.","Escribíamos un libro."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Ellas bebían vino.", answers:["They were drinking wine.","They used to drink wine."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"They were drinking wine.", answers:["Ellas bebían vino.","Ellos bebían vino.","Bebían vino."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"They were used to drink wine.", answers:["Ellas bebían vino.","Ellos bebían vino.","Bebían vino."],language:"Spanish"},				
	{question:"I was drinking wine.", answers:["Yo bebía vino.","Bebía vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"I used to drink wine.", answers:["Yo bebía vino.","Bebía vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Yo bebía vino.", answers:["I was drinking wine.","I used to drink wine."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Tú leías el libro.", answers:["You were reading the book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You were reading the book.", answers:["Tú leías el libro.","Leías el libro.","Usted leía el libro.","Ustedes leían el libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Las niñas escribían.", answers:["The girls were writing.","The children were writing.","The girls used to write.","The children used to write."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls were writing.", answers:["Las niñas escribían."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"The girls used to write.", answers:["Las niñas escribían."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo leía.", answers:["I was reading.","I used to read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I was reading.", answers:["Yo leía.","Leía."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I used to read.", answers:["Yo leía.","Leía."], language:"English"},
	{question:"El niño leía.", answers:["The boy was reading.","The child was reading.","The boy used to read.","The child used to read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boy was reading.", answers:["El niño leía."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boy used to read.", answers:["El niño leía."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotros leíamos un diario.", answers:["We were reading a newspaper."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotras leíamos un diario.", answers:["We were reading a newspaper."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We were reading a newspaper.", answers:["Nosotros leíamos un diario.","Nosotras leíamos un diario.","Leíamos un diario."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellas leían.", answers:["They were reading.","The used to read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They were reading.", answers:["Ellas leían.","Ellos leían.","Leían."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos leían un libro.", answers:["They were reading a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They were reading a book.", answers:["Ellas leían un libro.","Ellos leían un libro.","Leían un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Nosotras comíamos arroz.", answers:["We were eating rice.","We used to eat rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotros comíamos arroz.", answers:["We were eating rice.","We used to eat rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We used to eat rice.", answers:["Nosotras comíamos arroz.","Nosotros comíamos arroz.","Comíamos arroz."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"We were eating rice.", answers:["Nosotras comíamos arroz.","Nosotros comíamos arroz.","Comíamos arroz."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo cocinaba pescado.", answers:["I was cooking fish.","I used to cook fish."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I was cooking fish.", answers:["Yo cocinaba pescado.","Cocinaba pescado."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"I used to cook fish.", answers:["Yo cocinaba pescado.","Cocinaba pescado."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos no comían nada.", answers:["They were not eating anything.","They weren't eating anything.","They didn't use to eat anything.","They did not use to eat anything."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They were not eating anything.", answers:["Ellos no comían nada.","Ellas no comían nada.","No comían nada."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No cocinaba.", answers:["I was not cooking.","I wasn't cooking.","I did not use to cook.","I didn't use to cook."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I was not cooking.", answers:["Yo no cocinaba.","No cocinaba."], language:"Spanish"}
	
	]);
